okay M as well as axes those are some of
the stocks that are looking attractive
but uh looks like we're back up in trade
and we're wrapping in above the 10,100
marks so not quite uh seeing the kind of
Stellar performance that we witnessed
just a couple of days ago but
nonetheless we seem to have recoup lost
ground quite convincingly so 90 points
higher on the Nifty is where we're
shutting shop pretty much in today's
trading session
10,138 there above out with the sensex
up 350 points and uh the broader
universe is well playing catch up it's a
bread that's very healthy and it's the
Nifty bank that's really done a lot of
the heavy lifting in today's trading
session it's the financials alone uh
that have really managed to hold out in
trade and support the Frontline index in
fact as we just flagged off a short
while ago rbl Bank 169 on that stock
it's really uh you know gained quite a
bit of traction in the past few trading
sessions and today's an exceptional
performance indicon Bank pnb bundan
kotak SBI put your finger on any of
those names and they're Up and Away in
today's trading session on the Frontline
index apart from financials well you've
got hindalco up about 3% there's R which
sits pretty at 1576 by the time we wind
it down uh Shri cement TCS vidanta Tech
Mahindra jsw steel as well as grm and
HCL Technologies along with HL have been
some of the other commendable Movers on
the downside though hero Moto struggles
a bit Gil in the red Titan Bajaj Auto
onc as well as L&T and UPL those have
been some of the stocks that have had it
a bit rough in today's trading session
going to take you through then some of
the news makers in today's trading
session and uh well clearly hero Moto
has been uh in Focus post the kind of
numbers management very optimistic mid
rural uh
Revival but the covid induced vot
certainly hurt their overall margin
picture ever already um active in trade
the Burman family according to sources
we understand could be in as a white
night and infus capital in their
personal capacity gcpl has been a news
maker a sharp Knockin trade you have the
mdn CEO which is VI gambir who has
stepped down and it is naaba godri who
will be uh filling his shoes H in the
annual report said that there have been
Co Le disruptions which have impacted
growth but going forward they are
confident of managing the crisis Titan
as well the management saying that the
new normal will only last a few months
there will be smarter opportunities
going forward you've also had something
like Bombay danging reeling under
pressure on the back of its numbers team
lease a loss of 29 CR rupees mry had a
city cell rating on the stock with a 760
rupe Target price some of those
exhibition players have been uh continue
to remain under quite a bit of pressure
PVR as well as Inox in today's trade
have been down and out and you've also
got
maruti within the autosphere that's been
in Focus their production and may
slumping nearly
98% owing to the lockdown within the mid
end the small caps then just going to
highlight some of the stocks that have
been very active in today's trading
session apart from rbl bank there's been
Dishman caroen time technoplast Kaplan
Point nbcc granules India and barag that
have really sha in trade today so all in
all ABA uh after all the give and take
10,100 on the
screen yes we seem to be stuck there for
now aan but uh kunj I know you said
earlier cautious is the way to go uh
we're watching out of course for any
move from the fed this week that's one
trigger point other than that however
markets have seemed very very volatile
at least in the last couple of sessions
so you know going ahead just some
closing comments in terms of what really
to watch out
for terms of Market frankly I wouldn't
call it volatile I will call it more of
consolidation uh and which is quite
healthy so after a sharp 10% move in
hardly less than 10 trading sessions
it's high time that the market takes a
breather uh before taking any further
Direction uh looks difficult that it
could be on the upward side of course
one cannot predict the market ever
especially in the short term uh the
triggers you rightly said uh that going
forward we will have to watch out for
March quarter result season is more or
less over which has been on the expected
lines we are already in the month of
June uh so now June quarter results uh
will be the other uh trigger to watch
out for of course most of the companies
across the sectors have already given uh
the the uh not guidance but the Outlook
that okay what has been the pressure and
and those are very well known sectors
like automobile consumer durables almost
and a half months uh 1 and a half
quarter uh I'm sorry half quarter that
is 1 and a half month sales are are
completely wiped out so in terms of
investment opportunity if one has to
look at in the current market uh to be
on safer side in in case of any uh
downward movement should participate
into those stocks which have not moved
up in line with the recent recovery so
one such a stock which comes to my mind
is a bti airel so that's a stock which
which uh actually came down post the
sharp upward movement it had after the
result and then there was a promoter
stake sale and since then it has been
trying to consolidate uh the the
medium-term Outlook looks good not one
of the sectors which are clear wash out
because of the lockdown Telecom is
something which has been demand as an
ongoing basis in fact if at all the
sector has seen increased demand mainly
coming from the data site so so that's
that's something I would like to
recommend all right
we'll okay wonderful and that seems to
be there seem to be resounding calls on
B I think Canal was also pointing it out
earlier so both fundamental and
Technical sounding very bullish there
we'll leave it for now thanks for
joining us CK thank you as well i' look
forward to catching up tomorrow that's
all from us for now
[Music]